1

PRIVACY NOTICE

We at Key Games Network B.V. (“Key Games”, “Azerion Casual” “we”, “us” or “our”)

respect your privacy and recognise the importance of providing a secure environment for

your personal data. Therefore, we are committed to being transparent about how we

collect and process your personal data.

The purpose of this privacy notice (“Privacy Notice”) is to inform you as a user about why

and how we process your personal data (that is any information that can be linked or

attributed to you, (“Personal Data”) when you play our games that link to this Privacy

Notice (“Games”). This includes information regarding with whom we will share your

Personal Data, how long we will retain it, and which rights you have in relation to the

processing.

In this Privacy Notice, we will give you general information about how we process your

Personal Data. We will furthermore give you more detailed information on the specific

processes within our Games.

I. GENERAL INFORMATION

In this part of our Privacy Notice, you will find general information about how we process

your Personal Data when you play our Games. For specific information with more details

about our processing activities, please see the specific information below.

II. Who is Responsible for the processing of your Personal Data?

Key Games Network B.V. Boeingavenue 30 1119PE SCHIPHOL\-RIJK, Netherlands is

responsible (“the Data Controller”) for the processing of your Personal Data.

2

1. Information Specific to My Dolphin Show and Play Along

Miffy Games

This section includes information specific to the data processing activities for My

Dolphin Show and Play Along Miffy games.

Please note that if a game is for children or for a mixed audience, we do not serve

interest-based advertising. We also do not actively collect information from users

when they play a game directed at children.

1.1. What information does Azerion collect?

Azerion collects certain information when you play our Games. As a general principle,

we do not collect and do not ask you to provide any “special categories of Personal

Data”, which is any particularly protected information such as data concerning

health, religion, political opinions or philosophical beliefs, sexual preferences or

orientation. We may also collect information from third parties such as payment

service providers.

We process the following types of your Personal Data:

1.1.1. Personal Data provided by you:

Information provided in relation to our customer service: When you contact

support, we collect your contact details (your username and your email address),

information about your request (subject and content of your request), and your

device information (IP address for location analysis, device ID and user ID).

Information provided in relation to transaction and payment: When you make

a purchase on our Games (e.g. new characters, skins or outfits) we collect information

which is related to your transaction, for example the payment method, purchased

items and date. We do not collect any card data or financial information, you will be

redirected to app stores acting as payment providers for the transaction of your

payment; we only receive payment confirmation details from our payment provider.

Information provided via social media: We manage various social media accounts

and fan pages for our games. When you contact our fan pages, we collect your social

media account details (your name or username and your profile photo) and

information about your correspondence (contents of your message).

1.1.2. Personal Data we receive or generate from your use of our Games

Your usage: We collect information about how you play our Games. This information

includes the actions you take within the game (e.g. your achievements such as the

3

level reached, the items purchased within our Games and the amount you spent in

our Games), the time and duration of your activity. Part of this information will be

stored in your account (such as your in-game progress).

1.1.3. Personal Data we collect from third parties

Payment Providers: If you make an in-app purchase, the transaction will be

processed by a third-party payment provider and will be subject to privacy policies of

third-party payment providers. For these transactions, we do not receive any

complete financial information (such as your full credit card information) but receive

information which is related to your transaction, for example the payment method,

amount, status and date.

1.2. For What Purpose Do We Process Your Personal Data?

When you play our Games, we use the information that we have about you:

● To provide you with our Games and associated websites, and continuously

improve their features;

● To store your gaming history;

● To provide help desk and support services;

● To analyze the functioning of the Game and associated websites;

● To enable in-app purchases;

● To prevent fraud and crime;

● To enforce our policies and terms of use

● To meet legal and tax obligations.

● To determine the legal requirements for processing of your Personal Data

(based on your location and your age)

● To keep records related to purchases

1.3. On which legal basis do we process your Personal Data?

Performance of a contract: We process your Personal Data for the performance of a

contract or to take steps prior to entering into a contract to which you are a party.

For example, where it is necessary to process your in\-game purchase and the

associated payment, in context of customer service, to support the operation of the

game or facilitate the delivery of requested services.

4

Compliance with legal obligations to which we are subject: We process your

Personal Data to comply with legal obligations, for example, in order to verify your

age, for tax and accounting purposes or legal disputes.

Legitimate interests: We also process your Personal Data to the extent that the

processing is necessary for our legitimate interests or those of third parties while

applying appropriate safeguards that protect your privacy.

1.4. Where will my Personal Data be processed?

Our Games are hosted within the European Economic Area (EEA) and your personal

data will be stored by Azerion in the EEA. To the extent that your personal data is

processed by our partners in a country outside of the EEA, we have taken all such

measures as are necessary to ensure an adequate level of protection for your

personal data in accordance with the requirements of applicable data protection

legislation including the execution of the European Commission’s standard data

protection clauses (also known as Model Clauses).

1.5. How long do we store your Personal Data?

Your personal data will only be stored for a period necessary for your use of our

Games for the purposes as described in this Privacy Notice or necessary for the

establishment, exercise of defense of legal claims or resolving disputes. Afterwards,

we will delete or anonymize your Personal Data. Please note that you always have

the right to request erasure of your personal data, after which we will take reasonable

measures to delete your personal data. However, you acknowledge that even if you

have requested deletion of your personal data, we may retain some information.

1.6. Which third parties have access to your data?

We will not disclose your Personal Data to any party who is not authorised to process

them. To manage our Games, we will share your Personal Data internally with

members of our responsible departments, technical support or customer support

involved in the gaming process and in each case only if access to your Personal Data

is necessary for the performance of their roles.

Moreover, and only when necessary to fulfil the purposes mentioned above, we

disclose your Personal Data to the following recipients or categories of recipients or

allow the following third parties to collect your Personal Data in connection with your

use of our Games. If you have any questions about how these third parties use your

information, we recommend you review their policies and contact them directly.:

Hosting and content delivery: Our Games are hosted by external companies

providing servers. Every time you make a request, for example by clicking on a link

5

on our Games, the information allowing this request (e.g. device information and

information on requested content) as well as online identifiers (your IP address) will

be sent to the external servers. This data is used to show you the content you

requested. We process this data on the basis of legitimate interest, to provide our

Games and ensure their functionality.

Payment Service Providers: Azerion may also use third-party payment service

providers (“PSP”), offering payment transaction services to Azerion in order to sell a

product or service through our Games. The PSP acts a data controller with regards to

the personal data related to the transactions processed for the purpose of purchasing

the product or service. The transaction data may include your personal details, your

payment card details, and the transaction details. Whenever you buy something in

our Games (e.g., a virtual game item), the information that you provide to the PSP is

subject to their privacy policies, not ours. The legal basis for this processing is the

performance of a contract. After you have purchased a product or service, Azerion

and the PSP have a legal requirement to retain your information for a legally

determined period of at least 7 years. Azerion shall be allowed to notify a PSP

regarding a user that engages in (or who a party believes has engaged in) any activity

that is illegal, that violates any person’s rights, or that led to such a user’s suspension

or termination of use of the Games. Azerion shall be allowed to notify a PSP regarding

a user who engages in (or who a party believes has engaged in) any activity that is

illegal, that violates any person’s rights, or that resulted in such user’s suspension or

termination of use of a Game.

Customer Support Partners: Azerion uses third party service providers in order to

offer our users customer support services. We may share personal data such as the

communication content, IP address, email address, and username (“Correspondence

Data”) with these partners. The Correspondence Data may be processed by Azerion

and business partners for the purpose of communication with you, blocking users,

changing email addresses, reactivating or blocking accounts, adding or removing in\-

game items, and other customer support services. The legal basis for the processing

of the Correspondence Data is performance of contract.

Partner networks: Azerion may use partner network providers who assist us to

distribute the Game in order to enable as many gamers as possible to play the Game.

Law enforcement, government authorities or courts: We disclose your Personal Data

in response to lawful requests from public authorities, including law enforcement,

government authorities, supervisory authorities or courts.

Other third parties: We also disclose your Personal Data in the event of any

contemplated or actual reorganization, merger, sale, joint venture, assignment,

6

transfer or other disposition of all or any portion of our business or assets (including

in any insolvency or similar proceedings).

1.7. Your rights

To the extent permitted by applicable data protection laws and regulations, you have

the following rights in relation to your Personal Data:

● Access to the Personal Data we hold about you

● Request the update or correction of your Personal Data

● Receive your Personal Data in a structured, commonly used and machine\-

readable format

● Request the deletion of your Personal Data where there is no good reason for

us to continue to process it

● Restrict the processing of your Personal Data

● Withdraw your consent

● Right to object

If you wish to exercise these rights, you can by sending a written request to Azerion

B.V., Beechavenue 182 1119 PX, Schiphol-Rijk, The Netherlands, detailing your

request, (to prevent misuse of requests for information), or sending an email

containing your request to: dpo@azerion.com.

Azerion does not knowingly process personal data from anyone under the age of 16

without parental consent. In the event we find out that we have processed personal

data of anyone under the age of 16 without parental consent, we will promptly delete

such data. Parents of users under the age of 16: if you wish to have access to your

child’s personal data to view, correct, or delete the information that we have

collected about your child, please send a written request to Azerion B.V.,

Beechavenue 182 1119 PX, Schiphol-Rijk, the Netherlands, detailing your request

along with a copy of your passport (to prevent misuse of requests for information),

or send an email with all such information to dpo@azerion.com. After verification,

the copy of your passport will be shredded.

In the event you have any questions or concerns in relation to the processing of your

personal data, you can send an email to our Data Protection Officer by email at

dpo@azerion.com.

7

If you are not satisfied with our responses and/or support to resolve your concerns,

you have the right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority, in particular in

the European Union (or European Economic Area) Member State where you work,

normally live, or where any alleged infringement of data protection laws occurred.

2. Information On Other Games

2.1. What types of Personal Data do we process and how do we

collect it?

When you play our Games, we collect, use, store and transfer different kinds of Personal

Data. As a general principle, we do not collect and do not ask you to provide any “special

categories of Personal Data”, which is any particularly protected information such as data

concerning health, religion, political opinions or philosophical beliefs, sexual preferences or

orientation.

The information we collect depends on which of our Games you have played and how you

have played them. We process the following types of your Personal Data:

2.1.1. Personal Data provided by you

When you use our Games, you provide or be asked to provide us certain information,

including:

● Information provided in relation to our customer service: When you contact

support, we collect your contact details (your username and your email address),

information about your request (subject and content of your request), and your

device information (IP address for location analysis, device ID and user ID).

● Information provided in relation to transaction and payment: When you make a

purchase on our Games (e.g. purchased items, extra in\-game lives, hints to clear a

level or removing ads via payment) we collect information which is related to your

transaction, for example device information, country, region and the postal code.

We do not collect any card data, you will be redirected to appstores acting as

payment providers for the transaction of your payment, we only receive payment

8

confirmation details from our payment provider. For more information, please see

the service specific information below.

● Information provided via social media: We manage various social media accounts

and fan pages for our games. When you contact with our fan pages, we collect your

social media account details (your name or username and your profile photo) and

information about your correspondence (contents of your message). Never share

information or personal data that is harmful for yourself or others.

● Your profile information: In some of our Games, you need to create a player profile

that other players can see. When you create a player profile, we collect profile

information provided by you to personalize your profile (such as a nickname or

character name, flag of a country chosen by you as part of your profile and

customized outfit of your avatar). This information will be combined with your user

ID.

2.1.2. Personal Data we receive or generate from your play of our

Games

When you play our Games, we also process device\-related information and information

about how you interact with our Games, including:

● Technical information: We collect information about your device/device settings

you use for the purposes described below. The information we obtain from your

device(s) includes the type of your device, device ID(s), user ID, IDFA or Google

Advertising ID, online identifiers (your IP address), timestamp, geolocation data

(based on your IP address and limited to the country) and other technical

information.

● Your usage: We collect information about how you play our Games. This

information includes the actions you take within the game (e.g. your achievements

such as the level reached, the items purchased within our Games and the amount

you spent in our Games), the time and duration of your activity, and your interaction

9

with advertisements (clicks, instals and creative views). Furthermore, we collect

information about the websites or apps that led you to our Games. Part of this

information will be stored in your account (such as your in-game progress).

2.1.3. Personal Data we collect from third parties

In certain scenarios, we will also obtain your Personal Data from third parties, in strict

compliance with applicable data protection laws and regulations. Your Personal Data may

be provided by the following third parties:

● Payment Providers: If you make an in-app purchase, the transaction will be

processed by a third-party payment provider and will be subject to privacy policies

of third-party payment providers. For these transactions, we do not receive any

complete financial information (such as your full credit card information) but receive

information which is related to your transaction, for example the payment method,

amount, status and date.

● Social Networks and connected third-party platforms:

For some of our Games, you have an option to connect with your Facebook account

by using your credentials with our log-in process. We receive certain information

about you from Facebook such as your first and last name, your profile picture, your

email address, your Facebook user ID, age\-range and your authentication token. In

order to benefit from additional features in our Games (such as an achievement

system and leaderboards), you may also log-in with your Google Play Games or

Apple Game Center account. If you choose to log-in, we receive from Google or

Apple your game service username, email address, profile photo and levels reached

in the game service. To learn more about which data is processed when you use

these Games, please see the section with service specific information below.

● User acquisition companies: If you click on our advertisements shown to you in a

third-party network or platform, we will receive campaign information (the

campaign ID, clicks on our ads, creative views), information about installs of our

10

Games, your location, purchase data (purchase is made or not) and technical

identifiers (such as advertisement ID) from our user acquisition partners.

● Other third parties: We also receive information about your approximate

geolocation (the country you are located in) from third parties (e.g. Google). We use

this information to comply with our legal obligations applying to the processing of

your Personal Data, customize certain services to your location, and for fraud or

abuse prevention purposes.

To learn more about which data is processed when you play our Games, please see the

section with service specific information below.

2.2. For what purpose do we process your Personal Data?

Depending on which Games you are playing and which privacy settings you have selected,

we process your Personal Data for the following purposes:

Provision and improvement of our Games

● to allow you to play our Games

● to create and manage your profile

● to restore your account if you ever lose access

● to facilitate your purchase, to verify and confirm your payment

● to facilitate content sharing on social networks

● to provide technical support and respond to your requests

● to identify and correct any bugs/errors

● to indicate the popularity of our Games

● to assess the quality of our Games

● to understand and improve your experience

Personalization of your game experience

● to remember your preferred game settings

● to remember you next time you play one of Games

11

● to provide you personalised in-game offers

● to provide you rewards for daily log-ins to our Games

Marketing and analytics

● to deliver (targeted and non-targeted) advertising in our Games

● to show you advertisements for our Games on other websites or apps

● to measure the effectiveness of advertising

● to personalise advertising for you

● to pay our business partners for the promotion of our Games

● to send you push notifications, informing you about new content and in\-game offers

Prevention of fraud and illegal activity

● to investigate fraud and illegal behaviour in our Games

● to enforce our policies and terms of use

Compliance with our legal or regulatory obligations

● to determine the legal requirements for processing of your Personal Data (based on

your location and your age)

● to keep records related to purchases

● to respond to your requests related to your data subject rights

● to comply with our legal obligations (e.g. tax and accounting obligations)

● to inform you about any updates to this Privacy Notice

Please see the section with service specific information below for a more detailed

description of the purposes for which we process your Personal Data within our Games.

2.3. Do we engage in profiling activities?

If you consent to this via the consent management pop\-up when you first initiate some of

our Games, we use tracking mechanisms to track your Personal Data for profiling purposes.

This allow us to serve relevant content to you and adjust both our Games and ads to your

interests. You have the right to object to this type of processing and you can also go to your

12

in-game settings to review and amend your privacy choices related to this type of

processing at any time.

2.4. On which legal basis do we process your Personal Data?

We process your Personal Data for the purposes described in this Privacy Notice, based on

the following legal grounds:

● Your consent: We process your Personal Data if you have provided your consent for

a specific purpose. For example, when you initiate our Games for the first time, we

ask for your consent for the data processing in the context of showing you

personalised content, offers and recommendations and for showing you interest

based ads. You have the right to withdraw your consent at any time, for example by

changing your in-game settings. Alternatively, you can always contact us from our

contact details below. Please note that this will not affect any processing carried

out before you withdraw your consent.

● Performance of a contract: We process your Personal Data for the performance of

a contract or to take steps prior to entering into a contract to which you are a party.

For example, where it is necessary to process your in\-game purchase and the

associated payment, in context of customer service, to support the operation of the

game or facilitate the delivery of requested services.

● Compliance with legal obligations to which we are subject: We process your

Personal Data to comply with legal obligations, for example, in order to verify your

age, for tax and accounting purposes or legal disputes.

● Legitimate interests: We also process your Personal Data to the extent that the

processing is necessary for our legitimate interests or those of third parties while

applying appropriate safeguards that protect your privacy. For example, we process

your Personal Data for improvement of our Games provided to you or to provide

you with a better user experience.

Please see for additional information the section with service specific information below.

13

2.5. With whom do we share your Personal Data?

We will not disclose your Personal Data to any party who is not authorised to process them.

To manage our Games, we will share your Personal Data internally with members of our

responsible departments, technical support or customer support involved in the gaming

process and in each case only if access to your Personal Data is necessary for the

performance of their roles.

Moreover, and only when necessary to fulfil the purposes mentioned above, we disclose

your Personal Data to the following recipients or categories of recipients or allow the

following third parties to collect your Personal Data in connection with your use of our

Games. If you have any questions about how these third parties use your information, we

recommend you review their policies and contact them directly.:

● External service providers: We share your Personal Data with external service

providers who perform services on our behalf, like customer support services, IT

services, analytics services and marketing services. Where we share your Personal

Data with external service providers, we have appropriate agreements in place to

ensure that your Personal Data is processed in compliance with applicable data

protection laws.

● Backend as a service providers: In order to improve our development productivity

while delivering high-quality games to you, we use backend as a service platform in

our Games. These platforms automate backend side development for us so that we

only have to write and maintain the frontend. In other words, our Games do not

need to contain all the code in themselves and instead they fetch information from

the backend as a service solution. All features in our Games that you interact with

such as advertisements, in-game purchases, daily rewards and push notifications

are provided via a backend as a service tool. We share your Personal Data with the

backend as a service provider to deliver our games to you and for maintaining our

games. Backend as a service provider also offers analytics services and we share

14

your personal data in this respect to be able to understand how well our games

perform.

● Payment providers: If you make in\-app purchases, the transaction will be processed

by a third-party payment provider and will be subject to the privacy policies of third

party providers.

● External advertising companies: With your consent, we share your Personal Data

with third-party advertising companies or allow third\-party advertising companies

to collect your Personal Data when you use our Games. If you choose not to receive

personalised ads at all, we will still show you ads, but they may not reflect your

interests as those ads will be content specific and not user specific. Please note that

by clicking on a third-party advertisement, you may be redirected to the third\-party

advertiser’s environment over which the third party is in control.

● Social networks and connected third-party platforms: For a number of our Games,

we have included a share button which enables you to share certain content on

social media. Once you press the button, you will be asked to log-in with your social

media platform credentials or other application credentials (such as your email

address for email apps or your phone number for sharing content on messengers).

In this case, the content you want to share (e.g. a screenshot from the game or your

high score) will be sent to the respective social network or third\-party platform.

● For some of our Games, you will find a Facebook share button which enables you to

share certain content on your Facebook timeline. Once you press the button, you

will be asked to log-in to your Facebook profile. In this case, the content you want

to share (e.g. a screenshot from the game or your high score) will be sent to

Facebook. Please be aware that because of how Facebook and its share function

works, Facebook collects data (such as your IP address and device information) even

if you do not use the share button.

● We have included a Facebook and Google Play Games button on our Games and

Apple Game Center login on our iOS version to enable users to integrate with their

15

social media profiles as and when they see fit to do so. Such parties may capture

some of your data that way. Please be aware that because of how Facebook and

Facebook Connect works, Facebook collects data (such as your IP address and device

information) even if you do not log\-in and do not use applications via Facebook.

These parties are data controllers of the data collected through log-in for their own

purposes.

● In order to increase the competitiveness for a few of our Games, we encourage you

to interact with other players. If you play these Games with your Facebook account,

your Facebook friends who also play our Games will see your name, photo, player

profile (which may include the information described above in Personal Data

provided by you), and descriptions of your in-game activity. Your Facebook friends

will also be able to interact with you through in-game activities such as comparing

high scores or sharing extra lives.

● Law enforcement, government authorities or courts: We disclose your Personal

Data in response to lawful requests from public authorities, including law

enforcement, government authorities, supervisory authorities or courts.

● Other third parties: We also disclose your Personal Data in the event of any

contemplated or actual reorganisation, merger, sale, joint venture, assignment,

transfer or other disposition of all or any portion of our business or assets (including

in any insolvency or similar proceedings).

Please see the section with service specific information below for more information about

the third parties we share your data with. Furthermore, you can find the third parties your

Personal Data be shared with by clicking on the following link:

3rd party list

2.6. Where will my Personal Data be processed?

In general, your Personal Data is stored on servers within the European Union (EU)/the

European Economic Area (EEA). We have implemented appropriate safeguards to protect

16

your Personal Data when it is transferred outside the EU/EEA, including the execution of

the European Commission’s standard data protection clauses (also known as Model

Clauses) to provide safeguards for your Personal Data.

2.7. How do we protect your Personal Data?

We have implemented appropriate technical and organisational security measures

designed to protect your Personal Data against accidental, unlawful or unauthorised

destruction, loss, alteration, access, disclosure or use. We update and test our security

standards on an ongoing basis. In addition, we take reasonable steps to assure that third

parties to whom we transfer your Personal Data provide sufficient protection of Personal

Data.

2.8. How long do we store your Personal Data?

We will not retain your Personal Data longer than necessary to fulfil the purposes for which

the data was collected or to fulfil our legal obligations or necessary for the establishment,

exercise of defence of legal claims or resolving disputes. Afterwards, we will delete or

anonymize your Personal Data. Please note that you always have the right to request

erasure of your personal data, after which we will take reasonable measures to delete your

personal data. However, you acknowledge that even if you have requested deletion of your

personal data, we may retain some information after you have closed, or we have deleted,

your account with us.

2.9. What are your rights in respect of your Personal Data?

To the extent permitted by applicable data protection laws and regulations, you have the

following rights in relation to your Personal Data:

● Access to the Personal Data we hold about you

● Request the update or correction of your Personal Data

● Receive your Personal Data in a structured, commonly used and machine\-readable

format

17

● Request the deletion of your Personal Data where there is no good reason for us to

continue to process it

● Restrict the processing of your Personal Data

● Withdraw your consent

Right to object

In the event and to the extent that we process your Personal Data based on our legitimate

interests, you have the right to object to the processing on specific grounds relating to your

particular situation. In such cases we will no longer process your Personal Data unless we

have compelling legitimate grounds for the processing which override your interests, rights

and freedoms, or for the establishment, exercise or defence of legal claims.

You also have the right to object where we are processing your Personal Data for direct

marketing purposes (including profiling). In such a case, we will stop processing your

Personal Data for marketing purposes.

You can exercise these rights by sending a request to the contact details set out below,

providing your email address and other mandatory information (such as your user ID or

device ID) as well as a description of your request.

If you believe we have not complied with our obligations under applicable data protection

laws and regulations, you can lodge a complaint with a competent data protection

authority, for example the Autoriteit Persoonsgegevens in the Netherlands.

III. How can you contact us?

If you have any queries about this Privacy Notice or how we use your Personal Data or if

you wish to exercise any of your rights, please contact us via e\-mail to dpo@azerion.com.

IV. How often do we update this Privacy Notice?

We regularly review this Privacy Notice. When there is a material change that will have a

relevant impact on the processing of your Personal Data, we will inform you with a message

or notification on our Games.

18

This Privacy Notice was last updated on:

Version: Last Updated:

2.0 14.03.2024

V. Additional Information for California Residents

This section for California residents supplements the information provided in this Privacy

Notice and applies solely to players, and others who reside in the State of California. We

provide this section to comply with the California Consumer Privacy Act of 2018 (CCPA) and

the regulations issued under it; accordingly, this section addresses the specific

requirements of the CCPA and should be read together with this Privacy Notice.

We collect information that identifies, relates to, describes, references, is capable of being

associated with, or could reasonably be linked, directly or indirectly, with a particular

consumer or device. In particular, we have collected the following categories of personal

information (envisaged by the CCPA) from consumers within the last twelve (12) months:

Category A – Identifiers (such as your device identifier, demographic information \-such as

your country, your username, email address, any information you may choose to provide -

such as your age or your language-)

Category B\- Personal information categories listed in the California Customer Records

statute (Cal. Civ. Code § 1798.80(e))

Category D – Commercial information (such as purchase history)

Category F – Internet or other similar network activity (such as your interaction with our

ads, your IP address)

Category G – Geolocation data

The CCPA provides consumers (California residents) with specific rights regarding their

personal information.

19

You have the right to access specific information i.e. you may request that we disclose

certain information to you about our collection and use of your personal information over

the past 12 months.

You have the right to deletion which means that you may request that we delete any of

your personal information we collected from you and retained, subject to certain

exceptions.

You have the right to opt out of any sale of your personal data by us to third parties. Please

note that your right to opt out does not apply to our sharing of personal data with service

providers, who are parties we engage to perform a function on our behalf and are

contractually obligated to use the personal data only for that function.

You can exercise these rights by sending a request to the contact details set out above,

providing your name, your email address as well as a description of your request.

20

VI. SERVICE SPECIFIC INFORMATION

In this part of our Privacy Notice, you will find specific information on how your Personal

Data is processed. For general information about data processes that apply, please see

above.

Please note that this section is not applicable to My Dolphin Show and Play Along Miffy

games.

Hosting and content delivery:

Our Games are hosted by external companies providing servers. Every time you make a

request, for example by clicking on a link on our Games, the information allowing this

request (e.g. device information and information on requested content) as well as online

identifiers (your IP address) will be sent to the external servers. This data is used to show

you the content you requested. We process this data on the basis of legitimate interest, to

provide and improve our Games and ensure its functionality.

Age-gating and Consent:

For some of our Games, you have to be at least 13 or above years of age to play. When you

play these Games for the first time, we will ask your age bracket (0-12, 13-15 or 16+). Only

if you indicate being at over 13 or above years of age, you will be able to proceed and

provide (or not provide) your consent for our advertising, analytics and profiling activities,

obtained via a consent pop-up. We ask for your age bracket and your consent in order to

fulfil our legal obligation.

Some of our games are directed to children who are below the age of 13. We are doing our

utmost to not obtain any data other than strictly necessary to function in the games.

21

Creation/administration of your account:

In order to attach all content and items within our Games to you, we create an account in

an automated way based on a random user id. We store your account data (user ID and

device ID) based on the performance of a contract.

Furthermore, for our Games that requires to create a profile, we will store your

personalized profile’s in\-game progress and your virtual assets (customized outfits, in\-game

currency).

If you choose to register using your Facebook, Google Play Games or Apple Game Center

account, we receive certain information about you from the respective third\-party provider

like e.g. your name, your profile picture, your email address and an authentication token.

This information will be stored for your account’s lifetime to ensure that your in-game

progress and information is connected with the third\-party platform and that you can log\-

in with your credentials.

Your account data will be stored for as long as your account exists, based on the

performance of a contract. You can delete your account at any time, for example by

submitting a deletion request by contacting our Data Protection Officer through sending an

email to dpo@azerion.com. We may retain your account data after a deletion request due

to legal or regulatory requirements or for the reasons stated in this Privacy Notice.

Facebook Connect

We are offering you the opportunity to sign up for some of our Games through Facebook

Connect. In order to do this, you will be redirected to Facebook where you can log-in using

your Facebook account. Afterwards, your Facebook account will then be linked to our

Games.

Depending on your Facebook settings, linking your account will allow the following data to

be transmitted to us and/or retrieved by us: email address, name, profile photo and other

data that you have set to the public on your Facebook profile.

22

We shall only use this information for identification purposes and contract processing. For

more information on Facebook Connect and the privacy settings, please refer to the

Privacy Policy and Terms of Use of Facebook Inc.

If you use Facebook Connect to register for and log into an account, your Personal Data

will be transmitted to Facebook, Inc. 1601 Willow Road Menlo Park, California 94025 in

the United States.

You can unlink the accounts at any time and revoke the transfer of data with future effect

by changing your settings on Facebook (here) and through in-game settings menu.

Google Play Games

Our Games also employs the Google Play Games sign\-in button, which is operated by

Google Inc., 1600 Amphitheatre Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, United States

(Google). The link can be identified by a “joystick” symbol available in the main menu of

Games.

We are offering you the opportunity to sign-in for our Games through Google Play Games

in order to benefit from additional features in our Games (such as an achievement system

and global leaderboards). To do this, you will be redirected to Google where you can log

in using your Google user data. Your Google Play Games account will then be linked to our

Games.

Please note that you are able to play our Games without logging\-in via Google Play Games;

our full function with only missing features will be the ones provided by Google.

Depending on your Google settings, linking your account will allow the following data to

be transmitted to us and/or retrieved by us: username, email address, profile photo,

friends list and levels reached in the service, including any personal information you have

made publicly available on your Google profile.

23

We shall only use this information for identification purposes and contract processing. For

more information on Google and the privacy settings, please refer to the Privacy Policy and

Terms of Use of Google Inc.

The purpose and scope of data collection via Google, the processing and use of such data,

as well as your rights thereof and personal settings regarding privacy protection can be

found in the Google privacy settings section https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en-US

You can unlink the accounts at any time and revoke the transfer of data with future effect

by changing your settings on Google (here).

Apple Game Center

You may also sign-in to our Games by your Apple Game Center in order to benefit from

additional features in our Games (such as an achievement system and global

leaderboards). To do this, you will be redirected to Apple where you can log in using your

Apple user data. Your Apple Game Center account will then be linked to our Games.

Depending on your settings, linking your account will allow the following data to be

transmitted to us and/or retrieved by us: username, email address, profile photo and levels

reached in the service, including any personal information you have made publicly

available on your Google profile.

For more information on Apple and the privacy settings, please refer to the Apple Privacy

Policy at: https://www.apple.com/legal/privacy/en-ww/

Facebook Integration:

In order to make our Games more interactive experiences, some of our Games are

integrated with Facebook. Our Facebook integrated Games offer you Facebook as

more than just a log-in service. If you prefer, Facebook can become part of your

gaming experience. For instance, you can ask lives from your Facebook friends when

you are out of them or you can seek assistance (hints) from your Facebook friends.

Depending on your Facebook settings, your account will allow the same data as

24

Facebook Connect to be transmitted to us and/or retrieved by us: email address,

name, profile photo and other data that you have set to the public on your Facebook

profile.

Azerion Connect:

Azerion Connect provides a single sign on (SSO) service by generating a unique user

ID for each user. The user ID is recognised and verified by all third party platforms,

portals and services that are part of the Azerion Connect ecosystem. Azerion Connect

collects information about the users’ device/device settings and may combine this

information across the different devices.

The information Azerion Connect obtains from the devices include the device type,

the device ID, platform/portal/service ID (client id), country, screen resolution, the

creation date of the data record and the user ID assigned to the user.

Azerion Connect doesn’t share any personal data with any third party platforms.

The legal basis of processing the Personal Data is in Azerion Connect’s legitimate

interest.

Customer Support:

If you contact us for customer support, an external customer service company will process

your email address and/or your username (optional), and the content of your request. In

order to provide you with support, this information will be processed together with your IP

address, device information (device ID, model, OS, game language, carrier), the user ID, user

segment, and the last steps taken within our Games. The request history is stored for your

account’s lifetime to enable handling of newer requests based on your previous request

and to improve our services.

We process this data on the basis of the performance of a contract as far as the information

is required to answer your request. The continued storage of your request history is based

on our legitimate interest, in order to improve our services and for potential legal disputes.

25

Payments:

If you make in-app purchases, you will be redirected to an external payment provider

(Google or Apple depending on your device) for the transaction of your payment.

The transactions will be processed by the third-party payment provider. While we do not

collect and do not receive any financial data (such as your bank account data), we collect or

receive from third-party payment providers the following information related to your

transaction: the purchased amount and item (product ID and transaction ID), your country

(for currency), your user ID, your device ID, device information (user agent), time stamp,

callback ID and the status of your payment.

We process your Personal Data in connection with your payments on the basis of the

performance of a contract in order to facilitate your in-game purchase.

Logging of all in-game activities:

In order to help you with any issues you might have with our Games, to understand how

our software works, and to investigate fraud and illegal behaviour in our Games, we collect

and store all the steps you take within them, together with the following information: your

account ID, your IP address and device information (user agent or mobile device

information), mobile advertising ID in our logs which.

This process is based on our legitimate interests to be able to analyse and solve any

potential issue with our Games.

Analytics:

We use various analytics services to understand which features you like in our Games, how

you use or interact with them and how well our Games perform. The analytics data helps

us to improve our Games for you, to develop new items and features, to find crashes, issues

and bugs in our Games.

26

For in\-game analytics services to measure the performance of interaction of our Games

with users, we process your in-game activities (such as your in-game purchases, gameplay

statistics), device information and user ID.

For generic analytics to measure technical performance of our Games, we process

information about your device, crash reports, and data generated from playing our Games,

such as technical data generated during playing. We process this information to improve

the performance of our Games.

We process this information based on consent.

Achievements and leaderboards:

Other than competitive features provided via Google Play Games or Apple Game Center,

for some of our Games, we also offer in\-game leaderboards to compare high scores with

other players and earn badges that show achieved in\-game milestones. For providing

achievements and leaderboards, we collect user id, score, milestone id (in\-game activities)

and callback id.

Daily challenges and rewards:

We reward our players that keep on playing our Games on a daily basis and offer them

awards in the form of either in-game currency or in-game items. We also aim to incentivize

players to play our Games consistently by offering new challenges, tasks or missions every

day that only lasts for 24 hours. In order to offer you daily stuff, we collect user ID, last login

date and timestamp. Please note that this information is stored on your device locally and

remains as long as our Games are installed on your device.

Third-party advertising within our game:

In our Games, we show advertising from different advertising companies. These

advertisements can be personalized or non\-personal content related (contextual) ads. In

order to show you personalized ads and only if you have provided your consent, we will use

27

third-party advertising companies to collect your Personal Data. The collected data includes

your device information, like IP address and device identifiers, your location data, your in\-

game activity (such as purchase events and your game play sessions), information regarding

the delivery of ads and your interaction with them.

You can adjust your privacy preferences at any time in your in\-game settings. If you choose

not to receive personalised ads at all, we will still show you ads, but they may not reflect

your interests as those ads will be content specific and not user specific.

For some of the ads shown in our Games, you can earn virtual currency if you watch the ads

(“rewarded ads”). In order to credit the virtual currency to your account, we process the

following Personal Data: your device type, device language, country and in\-game behaviour.

This process is based on our and third\-party advertising companies’ consent, to encourage

you to watch the ad and spend money for the product shown in the ad.

New user acquisition:

In order to acquire new users, we create advertisements (banners/videos) for our Games

and provide our advertisements to third-party user acquisition companies which show our

ads in their apps or on their websites. If you click on the banner/video shown to you in a

third-party app or on a third-party website, you will be redirected to the app stores (Google,

or Apple) where you can install our Games (or in this case, the specific game that you clicked

on the banner). The information that you have clicked/viewed the advertisement

(campaign information) will be sent from the user acquisition companies to an attribution

platform provider and will then be passed by Appsflyer to the app store. If you install one

of our Games, the campaign information will also be passed from the app store to us and

will be processed to measure the effectiveness of our advertisements. The described data

processing activities help us prevent fraud, to track and optimize our campaigns, and to

reward our user acquisition partners. This is based on our consent.

When you start playing our Games, we collect and share post install events (for example,

the level you reached within the game and purchase segments) either through the

28

Appsflyer SDK or directly with the user acquisition companies which helps them optimizing

their services. We share these post install events based on your consent.

Segmentation:

We collect information about your in-game behaviour (such as first paid, installation date,

last paid, last played, levels completed, milestones achieved, number of purchases, total

paid amount along with your user information) and we create user segments (groups of

users with similar in-game behaviour) and analyse how certain groups behave in our games.

Based on the segments that they are included, we show users customized shop inventory,

offers and promotions. Different in\-game items will be offered to different user segments.

This process is based on your consent.

Social media sharing service:

For a number of our Games, we have included a share button which enables you to share

certain content on social media. Once you press the button, you will be asked to log-in with

your social media platform credentials or other application credentials (such as your email

address for email apps or your phone number for sharing content on messengers). In this

case, the content you want to share (e.g. a screenshot from the game or your high score)

will be sent to the respective social network or third-party platform.

For some of our Games, you will find a Facebook share button which enables you to share

certain content on your Facebook timeline. Once you press the button, you will be asked to

log-in to your Facebook profile. In this case, the content you want to share (e.g. a screenshot

from the game or your high score) will be sent to Facebook. Please be aware that because

of how Facebook and its share function works, Facebook collects data (such as your IP

address and device information) even if you do not use the share button.

29

Push Notifications

In some of our Games, you can receive push notifications about new content and offers or

personal updates (such as your lives have been renewed). For this purpose, user notification

service will process information about the status of the push notification (notification

received/viewed) and device information. You can turn off the push notifications in your in\-

game settings (and also from the settings menu of your device) at any time.

Third parties:

If you click here, you will see an overview of the third parties we share your Personal Data

with, or that may share your Personal Data with us.
